Yo! There you go, all snorkeled up
Hey man! Ciao! Omri...
Nice to meet you.
So weird to be here.
No, I missed the turn.
And then there was...
Did you continue? There's snow over there.
and after I turned, without the chain, I couldn’t get out
Oh. That's the problem. Yeah.
There's a bit of snow
on the north side. Yeah.
And when it's getting a little bit
of inclination, then there’s no traction.
Beautiful. You had no trouble on this hill?
You have low gearing or not?
There you go.
Yeah, because you need it.
This is a Pajero inside
the first one
No, no, no, it's the same
part of the first generation Pajero.
Everything.
The but also the, the axles,
the traction, but the whole dashboard too?
no, I think it's a different
I mean, the drive chain is the same
Oh, look at that.
Cute little camper. it is
So, Yeah.
So we cut all those points, then
there's going to be two holes in there
to nail them down at the back,
and then the next stone
will sit on top of that nail, right
So it's covering it
so you can see there’s two nails
Okay.
there should be another long hammer
somewhere.
Yeah.
Maybe on the front on the scaffolding
That one can be drilled
Got this one on.
there's the break
Break!
Are you sure?
Yeah. you have it? Yea I got it
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you so much! You’re welcome
Super kind of you
More like a chocolate mousse.
That's amazing.
Yeah.
A dark day
This morning it was super clear
when we, took the wrong road first.
Yeah.
Got a pretty nice view on the valley
You guys like wine?
Absolutely.
make a little start
why not?
Do you ever cook back here sometimes?
Yes, more in summer
Like on a Sunday we make pancakes here
We have breakfast here.
It's really nice.
I also sit here often to upload the video, because the connection is fast.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
Yea, in the cabin it’s a bit slow
Yeah.
It's nice to have this
other kitchen still.
Yea that stone takes out all the energy
All right.
Smells really good! Thanks, Brandon
I hope you enjoy it.
Salt, pepper, if you need it
Let me know.
move some stones, and then
in the afternoon, maybe we have a look at the trailer
And then pick up more stones tomorrow
if we get there with the car
We’ll put 4 chains on. Do you have 4 chains as well?
I have two
They’re not exactly the size, they are bigger
Let's wake up Ela
That one looks good.
This?
Yeah,
Lets do the top layer
Because that’s the driest
So this is, polenta
Yeah,
we have polenta, I don’t know in English how it’s called
It's polenta
It's corn, mais, but
the meal is polenta
I think it's.
Yeah.
So this, like,
I really, I think mountain meal.
Here is mushrooms.
Like, a ragu or made of mushrooms
and, spinach there.
And some other things
you can add. Wow..! Good stuff
Thank you so much.
Thank you so much. Serve yourself.
Help yourself guys
Yeah, it’s getting a bit more light...
Some sun?
It’s warmer as i thought it’s gonna be
Yeah.
The temperatures are not so bad
the cloud is still there.
I'm so angry with that cloud. ]
Can you just move away?
Because I want to paint the mountains
and this and I want to make the...
the profile of the mountains.
But there is snow on top
no, I mean like a cloud
Yeah.
I think every every bend, I tried to go
one more, one more
And then the last one, it was just...
It didn’t smell so nice, so i said, OK...
There's a whole row of rental cars and broken trailers on the mountain
you’re good.
now i’m good
Yeah. It's pretty hard, right? Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Careful, don’t go too fast
3,2,1
slowly, little bit more
alright, lets do it
All right,
well done guys!
good thing done, wow
Pretty rough? in the back
It was fun.
should we start?
Sausage.
you have to take it off right here
don’t be shy
thank you
that yours? that’s for you, man
I already had two
I guess we all have three
Thank you.
Maybe you calculated with Ela
My potato was good to go, actually.
So did we say we had butter?
Yeah, yeah a bit.
Where's the butter? I can go get it.
Where's the butter and cheese?
in the door of the fridge.
There was also cheese?
I can also...
There.
Which kind of cheese?
there’s like a little triangle cheese
you want to grate it?
No we can just put it up.
Help is on the way.
hold it
Oh. Philadelphia?
Yea, the weather doesn’t change, huh?
Typical March weather, it kind of fits visually
also with the muddy... situation we just had
So we just have guys
is typically much money.
it’s getting worse and worse
When is the snow going to melt?
Is it May time, or?
It’s melting, today
But slow.
Slow.
When it's all gone it's
usually, I think end of march.
and then we get another shower in April often, but it will go quickly
OK, we can put some more stones on the roof
so the car is empty?
Yeah. Good.
So there.
So this triangle goes there? Yeah.
And then,
Oh. And here we need a few more.
The hammer...
Perfect.
lets go against the fence.
Nice.
Getting there slowly.
I think next week I’m able to finish the roof
Mortar in the ridge gap.
And that will be the last thing.
And some boards on the sides.
made a good progress this week.
I had to pick up a few more stones. 15,
because some of them broke and,
I miscalculated a bit too.
So it's a bit of a
logistical challenge.
We fetched the trailer
and the other trailer
I brought to the blacksmith, so it’s going to be welded.
But getting up the muddy hill here
it's a cool van.
That Mitsubishi.
What was it, Delica?
It's the same undercarriage as the Pajero.
The first version
Yeah.
Two of them were able
to get the load here, so that was great.
Slowly warming up.
Yeah. It's a muddy situation.
Yeah. It's
not the most beautiful part of the season.
March.
Melting snow, but nice to see it
warming up, like in the valley...
It's very slowly starting to get green.
A lot of flowers already start,
so, Yeah, it's beautiful.
It's getting better quickly now.